With the users' historical order, maybe 2 to 3 weeks, we divide users to different ranks.
Based on some algorithm to calculate weight, user with a higher frequency to make order, with larger amount of order made, will have higher rank。
For user with higher rank, we facilita the process of creating orders,maybe by omitting some security/identifying process since we have donw this a lot to the user,
or by pulling his request from the pending buffer, and put the order to the front of the queue.